Vanesa Gonzalez

Gvane1919@gmail.com

(302)507-0828

Carrer Summary

Although I have recently graduated from college and started a new career path, I have made progress in exploring different areas in the work field to know my strengths and have progressed in those areas. As shown, I've worked in multiple areas such as customer service, sales, managing, and marketing. As of recently I have directed my career path to a new area, that of software development. My goal is to enter this field of work and grow my career.

Work Experience

Service and Sales associate

Darren Moore State Farm Ins. and Fin Svc.

2017-Pressent

- The role of the job is to help with retaining current customers and multi-lining a household with more than one product.
- Billing/ payments service, quoting auto, home, commercial, life and health.

Shift Manager/ Store Marketing

Auntie Anne's

2016- present

- The role of this job is to manage a shift team, positions, manager duties and sales. This allowed to show my strengths in management, leadership, and teamwork which is essential when working with others.
- Marketing roll is important for our store as we are trying to understand the way the customer will go about buying our product.
- Duties include online promotion via Facebook, through our page and that of the shopping mall where the where located. Weekly company briefs and promotion for new product sales.

Catering and ball room attendant

Mende Hall Inn

2017-2018

- Work the weekend schedule parties, engagements, dinners.
- Worked with teams to clear out the reception area, and prep tables, silverware and decorations for the next party if needed.

Dietary Aid

Cadia Rehab

2016-2017

- Worked under the Dietary consultant to prepare meal specific to the dietary needs of the inhouse residence.
- Confirm and edit daily changes to meal orders.
- Deliver residence meals.

First Year -Tax Associate

H&R Block, Wilmington DE

- Tax season 2016: First year tax associate, connect calls, individual marketing
- Prepared Taxed for Customer, Current 1040, 1040ez
- Sales of emerald card and tax protection

Store Attendant

The Clean Scene

September 2012-January 2017

- Keep store, machines, tables clean and clear.
- Promoted sales with store products and services.
- Directed customers on the proper sued of washing machines.
- Daily open and closed store

Shift Manager

Burger King

2010-2012

- Hired as a team member and became proficient in all areas of the store. Was able to work the in and out on running the store.
- Promoted to Shift manager, duties in this position included: running the shift team, inventory, customer service, nightly deposits.

Education

Penn LPS- Full Stack Boot Camp

Nov 2020- Present (expected completion date June 2021)

 Learn through a rigorous curriculum that covers a full stack: HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript, jQuery, Express.js, React.js, Node.js, computer science, database theory, MongoDB, MySQL, Git, and more.

Wilmington University

September 2013- May 2018

BA in Business- Marketing

- Learned the different areas that makes up a business. Learned the
- market, medium and data used to capture the attention of a prospect buyer.

Delcastle Vo-Tech High School

September 2009- August 2013

Medical Assisting

- Focused studies: Medical Assisting, CPR certified
- Participated in HOSA competitions.
- Volunteer at in-school blood drives

Special Skills

- Bilingual: fluent Spanish, English
- Proficient in Microsoft Word, Excel and Power Point, Outlook
- Management Experience
- Customer Service Experience
- Invoice Preparation
- Tax advising
- Tax preparation